Welcome to our new module.
Here, we'll be learning about
how to close a project.
In this set of videos,
you'll learn to explain
why closing a project
is important,
determine when a
project is complete,
and outline the project
closing process.
We'll learn that closing
serves as an integral aspect
of the project and helps
avoid unfavorable scenarios.
We'll also learn that
completing a project and
closing a project are two
very different things.
We'll talk about how
your stakeholders and
clients fit into the
closing process.
We'll cover how
your team can help
you close a project
and how you can
use retrospective meetings to
improve your procedures
and processes.
We've touched on retrospectives
a bit in the previous module,
but you'll learn about them
here in a new context.
You will also learn that a
project isn't fully closed
until you've celebrated your
team for a job well done.
Then, we'll explore how
the closing process
works specifically for
you as a project manager.
We'll learn what kinds of
presentations and
documentation are
required for project managers to
properly close the project.
There's a lot to cover,
so let's start with an overview
of the closing process.
Meet me in the next video.